

Prerna Khurana

- C2-114, Jalvayu Towers, Sector 56, Gurugram 122011
- +91-9953940600
- prernakhurana10@gmail.com

SUMMARY:

Motivated Client Servicing professional and a dedicated team player with over 8 years of strong commitment to quality service and demonstrating leadership skills while training and guiding team members to achieve professional goals and the client to achieve business goals.

- Project Management
- Microsoft Office Expertise
- Key Account Management
- Team Handling

- Secondary Research
- PowerPoint Presentations
- Stakeholder Engagement
- Coaching & Mentoring

SKILLS:

ASSISTANT MANAGER, 03/2023 - Current

Deloitte USI- Gurugram

EXPERIENCE:

- Independently handling end-to-end project management of initiatives on the account which pertains to all account-based marketing, client relationship management, account strategy, account contracting, internal operations.
- Assist in the development and maintenance of account marketing assets, marketing campaigns, proposal assets, on-boarding/off-boarding assets and processes.
- Act as an advisor to the account leadership by sieving through information and providing perspective.
- Support information needs for client meetings, client facing materials, leadership presentations.
- Assist in the development and maintenance of account relationship tools including relationship map, organizational charts.
- Work with account leadership in developing and implementing the Confidentiality Information Program including on-boarding and off-boarding of team members.
- Coach and mentor the team on project management, client management, teaming, and other professional attributes.
- Conduct training sessions for process improvement
- Identify strengths of team members to provide them with opportunities and coach them in professional growth.

Sr. Associate Assurance - PMO, 11/2018 – 03/2023

EY - GDS – Gurugram

- Project Management for Global Assurance engagements with the assigned teams, through various processes, such as multi-location coordination, client account management.
- Independently work on critical engagements, projects which include implementing Standard Quality Management as and when required.
- Work with PPED and other stakeholders to understand their needs and provide excellent service throughout their Audit cycle.
- Act as a owner of all process related documents and ensured that they are up to date
- Review and present deliverables on assurance project status, risk and results while ensuring that the timelines are met.
- Review and present post engagement analysis, of assigned clients, showcasing- trends, KPI's and deep dive analysis.
- Manage the performance of team members through regular check-ins, providing timely feedback based on personal observations and client responses.
- Drive quality culture and promote process improvements in the team.

Deputy Manager, 07/2015 – 11/2018

Axis Bank - Delhi

- Manage banking operations effectively and efficiently inclusive of implementing short/long term plans.
- Ensure compliance to rules and regulations including latest circulars and notifications.
- Coordinate with various branches and managing a variety of branch banking operations.
- Strive to deliver customer delight by ensuring that the account plan aligned is with client objectives and interests in order to exceed the client expectations.
- Handle client portfolios and being responsible for activities such as customer acquisition and relationship management.
- Interface with the clients to understand their requirements and cultivate relations with them for customer retention and securing repeat business.

Expansion of Alumini Network (Internship), 05/2014 – 07/2014

EY - Gurugram

EDUCATION:

JIMS, Delhi, 2013/2015, Post Graduate Diploma in Management

Delhi University, 2009/2012, Bachelors of Business Economics

LANGUAGES:

- Hindi
- English